[
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "COMIDA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: CEHLEUP",
        "response": "PELUCHE" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "LAPTOP" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "RÁPIDO" 
    },
     {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "LÁPIZ" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "DULCE" 
    },{
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "MÚSICA" 
    },
     {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "LÍMITE" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "CÁMARA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "RETRATO" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "HÉLICE" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "TÚNEL" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "BAÑAR" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "MANJAR" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "CHISTE" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "BOSQUE" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "GRITAR" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "CUELLO" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "JARDÍN" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "MACETA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "PULGAR" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "CERRAR" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "LUCHAR" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "BLANCO" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "BRILLAR" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "BRILLO" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "CENIZA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "SOMBRA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "SUERTE" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "BOCINA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "JIRAFA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "COCHE" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "ESPUMA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "TRAMPA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "FLAUTA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "CUERDA" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "VENADO" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "PERRO" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Ordena la palabra: IDCMOA",
        "response": "ARDILLA" 
}
]
